tennis-x.com 2019-12-02

# Tennis-X.com Privacy Policy & Terms

**  
Tennis-X.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Tennis-X.com

**Personal Information**  
Your privacy is important at Tennis-X.com and we regard all personal information collected from visitors and subscribers as completely confidential. This includes personal data provided during any subscription registration or answering polls/surveys. Tennis-X.com may use these information solely for internal purposes and will not sell, loan or share these information with any third party for whatever purpose.If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet, we will keep that information private unless expressly stated otherwise. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data solely for trends and statistics research.

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com. 

**Advertisers**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

 **Public Forums & Blog Commenting**  
This site makes discussion boards and blog commenting available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these or any other areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Should you violate any of our [commenting guidelines](http://www.tennis-x.com/pages/commenting.php) we reserve the right to deny your postings. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites, and as such Tennis-X.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact
